[Music]
Madam, uh, may I take five, uh, little
bit of your time?
>> I want to promote. Not promote. Do you
guys have insurance already?
>> Oh, no. It's okay. I don't trust this
thing. Okay,
>> it's okay. Just ignore our mother
because she never trust about insurance.
>> Okay, I understand.
>> But may I know what kind of insurance
you promote?
>> Uh we prom
insurance which is uh we provide.
>> Yes, sure. We provide a lot of uh
insurance but today I more to medical
insurance because nowadays people always
uh ignore about their healthy about
their health about their mental health
everything.
>> So when something happened to their
siblings their family members they don't
have enough uh money to pay. So we here
>> come to help.
>> I think right now that's all from me.
>> Um sir can I have your business card? We
also won.
>> Oh, you guys also won. Yes, you guys are
sibling.
>> You think this and
>> if have any question, you know where to
contact me. All right.
>> All right. Thank you, sir. Thank you.
>> One day later.
>> Hey,
are you okay? Come, let's go to
hospital.
[Music]
Can you sign here, please?
>> This is your bill. Do you prefer to pay
with card or cash, ma'am?
>> Uh, cut.
>> Do you have any medical insurance?
>> Nope. I don't take any medical insurance
for my daughter.
>> Oh, that's bad. Mother, are you sure you
don't want to buy insurance?
>> Why do you think we need insurance?
Actually, insurance really important
nowadays because it can cover ourself.
But we still have our saving.
>> Yes, but it used a lot of money.
>> M I don't think so. We need mother. See,
yesterday you use your own money to pay
the bill hospital. You still don't want
to buy insurance.
>> Maybe I will think about it again.
>> It's okay. If you change your mind, you
can contact this agent. Agent of
insurance.
>> Okay.
>> Hello.
>> Is this insurance from potential?
>> Yeah, sure. I'm Adam from Predential
Insurance.
>> I think I'm interested to know about uh
potential insurance.
Can I know when you free because I think
I want to spend it on insurance.
>> Yeah, sure. We can meet face to face. I
think the best place that we can met is
at my office. Sure. I will give you
address and you can come here.
>> Okay. See you later.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> Four to six weeks later.
>> So, can you help me to explain more
about your package? First of all, I'm
sorry for what happening to your
daughter, your lovely daughter. I heard
that you pay all of the bill by your
own, right? It's okay. I think
alhamdulillah your daughter also getting
better right now. So, first of all, I
think I at Predential we have three
medical insurance, three products, three
package of medical insurance as you can
see here. The first one is PRU Millive.
The second one is PRU mill 2.0 old and
the third one is PR value that is the
the people who after 5 years old for the
newborn baby you have PU my is actually
P to prove my child plus that is the
newborn for the newborn but for your
daughter I you want to take for your
daughter
>> yes I want to take my medical insurance
for my daughter and she 19 years old
>> okay 19 years old daughter you want to
take insurance for her
>> yes
>> uh may I know your budget now M
200 below
>> for you with budget below 200 or around
200 we will have uh a package name
value 2.0 which is only two per 100 per
month and the scope of cover is all
about the charge uh at the hospital
hospital if you don't if your daughter
or you has been hospitalized have been
wed you can uh this insurance can
protect you by uh paying all of the
cost. All right. And then also we have
uh for operation like transplant bone
and also the organ that is there I think
right now transplant also any operation
is high cost right.
>> Yes.
>> This package based on age or gender
>> this package uh is uh can be applied for
all of the genders and all of the age.
All right. But for the just now I have
say for the newborn baby we have other
package for the pro uh m newborn for the
newborn baby but this is uh suitable for
the adults for the uh teens teenage and
the welcomes. M
>> all right. Uh for the other benefit uh
such as if you uh if you or your
daughter or any of your family has been
uh awarded for operation such as
transplant, you need to do transplant,
you need to go, you need to do
operation, we also cover that part but
only once per lifetime. All right. But
if you want to no limit per lifetime, we
also have others. But the for the
booster one. All right.
This also with the same price 200, 300
and 400 can choose. All right. And then
uh that is the benefit. But uh for this
we not cover your sons or your daughter
or yourself uh after s after the
investig investig in
>> investigate
>> investigate. I'm sorry.
>> It's okay.
>> Is my quite tired today? Our
investigation finished. If we know that
the the alibi has uh bring us to that
your daughter or your son or anybody in
your family that covered by this
insurance hurt themselves I not cover
that part. Lastly we don't uh do for
claim benefits for preventive care and
that is uh for other package that is you
do do you need to do some supplies for
that part. If I want to proceed this
package, what should I do and what
should I bring to you for proceed this
package?
>> That's such a good question. Uh in here
we not uh too much of document the
interview. You can also apply uh online
at their website
>> or just just uh submit submit every
every document online and then our
insurance will approve it will uh give
you suggestion if you want to change
another package but if you want face to
face you just need to submit uh your uh
birth certificate s that related with
money like account number something like
that. Okay, thank you for all the
explanation. I think I interested for
this package and I think I will contact
you after this.
>> Okay, thank you also for trust us and I
hope this is this can bring us to a
brighter future. All right.